meetanshi.com 2018-12-26

# Privacy Policy | Meetanshi

At Meetanshi, we respect the importance of your privacy and obligate to protect your privacy.

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their 'Personally Identifiable Information' (PII) is being used online. PII is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.

### What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our website?

When ordering or registering on our site https://meetanshi.com/, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information or other details to help you with your transaction.

### When do we collect information?

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to a newsletter or fill out a form.

### How do we use your information?

Our prime objective to collect your information is to provide a smooth, relevant and secure browsing experience at our site. We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:  
             **•**  To personalize your experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.  
             **•**  To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.  
             **•**  To quickly process your transactions.  
             **•**  To ask for ratings and reviews of services or products  
             **•**  To follow up with them after correspondence (live chat, email or phone inquiries)

### How do we protect your information?

Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible. We use regular Malware Scanning. Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. We implement a variety of security measures when a user places an order enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information. All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers.

### You can choose not to share your Information

You can choose not to share your personal information with us in accordance with **GDPR**. This will not restrict you from visiting our site. You can still explore many parts of our website but depending on your choice some parts of the site or options may not be available to you which requires your personal information for us to better interact with you.

### Data Retention

When you place an order through the Site, we will maintain your Order Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.

### User Rights

If you are a European resident, you have the right to access the personal information we have about you and to ask that your personal information be updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below.

If you are a European resident, we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above.

### Public Information

Any information that you decide to publish on the publically available part of our website is automatically available to all users of that area of the site regardless of it being personal information. We advise you to only post information on the public area of the site which you deem suitable for all the user of that public area.

### Do we use 'cookies'?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

### We use cookies to:

             **•**  Help remember and process the items in the shopping cart.  
             **•**  Understand and save user's preferences for future visits.  
             **•**  Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third-party services that track this information on our behalf.  
You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since browser is a little different, look at your browser's Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you turn cookies off, some of the features that make your site experience more efficient may not function properly.

### Third-party disclosure

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information unless we provide users with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or serving our users, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release information when it's release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property or safety.  
However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

### Third-party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We, therefore, have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

### Google

Google's advertising requirements can be summed up by Google's Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. <https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en>

**We have implemented the following:**  
             **•**  Demographics and Interests Reporting  
We, along with third-party vendors such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.

**Opting out:**

Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative Opt Out page or by using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.

### How does our site handle Do Not Track signals?

We honor Do Not Track signals and Do Not Track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.

### Does our site allow third-party behavioral tracking?

It's also important to note that we allow third-party behavioral tracking

### Children Online Privacy Protection Act

We do not specifically market to children under the age of 18 years old. Accordingly, we do not collection Personally Identifiable Information for children under the age of 18 years.

### Fair Information Practices

In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:  
We will notify you via email  
             **•**  Within 7 business days  
We will notify the users via in-site notification  
             **•**  Within 7 business days

### CAN-SPAM Act

The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.  
To be in accordance with CAN-SPAM, we agree to the following:

**If at any time, you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us at help@meetanshi.com** and we will promptly remove you from **ALL**  correspondence.

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

Please note that we reserve the right to make changes to this privacy policy at any time without prior notice. So, we advise you to refer to this policy frequently. Any changes to the policy will take effect immediately upon publishing on the website. If we make material changes to this policy we will notify you so that you can be aware of how will we collect information from you and how will we use it.

### Contact Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us by e-mail at **help@meetanshi.com** or mail us at:

Meetanshi,  
#305, Eva Complex,  
Opp. Gulista Ground,   
Waghawadi Road,  
Hill Drive, Bhavnagar, Gujarat(India).
